My Lady,
please take the medicine first.
Cuijuan,
please deliver this letter
to Su...
to Mr. Chu Nanfeng in person.
Tell him
to meet me at the old place.
Yes, My Lady.
My Lady, please take the medicine.
What's this?
It's a Zutai Medicine given by the Old Lady.
She also told me to drink it for half a month.
She has the maid bring it to you every day.
If you find it bitter,
I'll make some osmanthus candied fruit for you.
I see. You can go.
OK.
What are you doing?
Don't be afraid, baby.
I'm here.
Don't be so high and mighty.
Once my sister
becomes the Young Madam,
the Ling family
will be ours.
You'll be rich and powerful.
Just do as I say.
Miss,
are you alright?
What does this have to do with you?
What do you want?
Trying to steal my thunder?
I'll teach you a lesson!
[I thought she was being bullied,]
[but it turns out to be a ruse.]
Your guest hasn't arrived yet.
Why are you in such a hurry to leave?
Xiaobai.
Sis.
She...
What did Xiaobai do wrong
to do this to him?
He's just a kid!
A kid?
He's a big kid!
Cousin,
I suspect
Xiaobai must have
caught you and Chu Nanfeng in the act,
which led to his brutal murder.
This letter says
you asked Chu Nanfeng to come to this room.
Come out.
Young Madam, please spare me.
Young Marshal and Miss Ye
saw me delivering the letter.
I dare not lie.
I can only tell the truth.
Cuijuan.
Do you know?
You smell so good.
This is the only box of Xiangfen Shuidiao Getou
in Yang City.
The scent can last a month.
If someone opens the letter,
she will be infected with this scent.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
I just asked my sister
to arrange a meeting with Chu Nanfeng.
Are you implying
my sister is shameless?
Yang City,
you're so unreasonable.
I can't even
meet my sister?
Young Marshal,
why didn't you
tell me about the rules?
Miss Ye,
since you like my servant so much,
I'll give her to you
as a gift.
Cuijuan,
I think Miss Ye likes you very much.
You two are also fated.
Why don't you be together?
Brother.
Let's go.
This is just a trap I set.
Thank you for your concern.
Su Muwan.
I'm just afraid of losing you.
Xiaobei.
Let's go to the hospital.
Qingming,
try this.
I brought it back from abroad.
It's really good.
Young Madam,
I'm sent here by Master Su Hong
to serve you.
I see.
You can go now.
Yes.
Qianyue,
take me
to the garden.
I heard Huai is there.
Huai.
Come on, we'll see.
This one looks good.
And a bow.
This one is suitable.
These shoes match the dress.
Your dress is pretty too.
Yeah, I think so.
You're a fake.
You don't like her?
No.
She's about to become your sister-in-law.
The Ye family
is like a bloodsucking leech,
clinging to our Ling family.
They make my brother arrange things
and take care of business.
I don't want such a person to be my sister-in-law.
After all, Ye Family is your grandmother's family.
Keep your voice down.
That's right.
Every woman
in Ye Family
is a blood bank for men.
Now it's a society of gender equality.
Ye Family
has set too many rules for women.
Let's go.
Leave them alone.
Okay.
It's done.
You're in love.
I really miss
the time when I wasn't a witch.
Yes.
Qianyue,
what were you talking about?
I said,
why bother?
You'll see him soon,
and even sing for him.
Oh, no,
you can't do that.
Qianyue,
look, look,
that's him.
Isn't he handsome?
Just so so,
not as handsome as my brother.
You really have no taste.
You!
So rude!
As an unmarried girl,
who allowed you to meet those men in the garden?
After two years of study,
you've become too independent.
I'm just telling the truth.
Ye Jinrou is also unmarried.
Why am I the only one being punished?
Madam,
Xueqiu is right.
I am unmarried,
and I shouldn't have been in the garden.
But I thought,
since I will be
getting married soon,
it would be good to get familiar with it.
Madam,
it's all my fault.
It's clearly your fault!
Why are you pretending to be a good person?
Damn it!
Shut up!
You made a mistake first,
and then you didn't respect the elder.
Jinrou is your future sister-in-law.
What kind of sister-in-law is she?
Su Muwan is the only sister-in-law.
You...
I'll beat you.
How dare you!
I...
You...
No way.
I took Xueqiu to the garden.
I have to protect her.
Madam,
this is my fault.
I'm willing to be punished.
Fuyuan.
Yes.
Take her away.
Copy the "Women's Rules" and "Women's Precepts" 300 times.
Let's go, Young Madam.
Young Madam,
you must think carefully.
With such a careless attitude,
you can't be the hostess of the mansion.
Look at this handwriting,
crooked and
disordered.
It doesn't show any sincerity from you.
Are you trying to get by
with this kind of thing?
This is written by our Young Madam herself.
For Xueqiu, I'll tolerate you.
But don't go too far.
You...
How dare you
speak to me like that?
I'm sent by the Old Madam.
Xiaoxue.
Stamp on it.